Amy it says you are trained in
technology that's very good
are you adept at Excel no PowerPoint no
publisher not really exactly in what
area of technology are you proficient
snapchat Pinterest Instagram vine
Twitter you know the big ones I'm
surprised you didn't save Facebook
that's our old people like my parents
well Amy when you're working for me you
have to have those kind of research
skills because I'll send you things for
you to comb through and get the answers
and send them to me so for that you've
got to be really good at technology
first stuff like that no problem I'll
just ask Siri you know just how Siri you
know Siri told me this area find me that
we're all good getting you the answers
tell Siri I want you ready to go at 8:00
sharp each and every morning
I don't understand what don't you
understand
what you just said you don't understand
be ready to go no you said 8:00 right
yes 8:00 like in the morning 8:00
yes in the morning yeah that kind of
doesn't work for me who gets up at 8:00
I do i Skype with my French boyfriend
and Paris until like 3:00 in the morning
I don't even get to Starbucks until like
10:00 where I order my grande chai tea
latte three pumps skim milk light water
2% foam extra hot but not too hot so if
it's okay I work best in the morning at
10:45 Wow baby I don't think we're gonna
be a good fit why are you so negative I
can sense your hostilities and right now
I am not feeling very safe I've been
here for over five minutes and the only
nice thing you have said to me was nice
resume
which I typed all night for this meeting
with you you've given me no guidance no
validation no encouragement no
supervision is there an HR director
somewhere HR director yes I need to
speak to someone I may have to take off
today it's a mental health day take
today off you Amy Amy look at me you
don't work here are you firing me okay
yes